{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Above Ground Pool Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/2102680/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":2102680,"taskName":"Swimming Pool - Above Ground - Build or Install","taskDescription":"Build or Install an Above Ground Swimming Pool","xmTaskDescriptor":"Above Ground Pool Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4615,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Swimming pool swim above ground","textMessagingName":"Aboveground Pool","rolloverLongDesc":"Above ground swimming pool installers.","rolloverShortDesc":"Above ground swimming pool installers.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build or Install an Above Ground Swimming Pool.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Above Ground Pool Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Swimming Pool Above Ground","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Above Ground Swimming Pool Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool - Above Ground, Build or Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-Above-Ground-Build-or-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Above Ground Pool Installation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Swimming,pool,swim,above,ground,sauna,hot,tub,lap","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":804,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/2102680/":{"taskOID":2102680,"originalTaskOID":2102680,"setID":804,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7585,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the pool for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7586,"questionDisplayText":"Type of pool install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of above ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","answerDisplayText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","answerDisplayText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7587,"questionDisplayText":"Shape of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What shape of above ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11550,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11551,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rectangle","answerDisplayText":"Rectangle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11552,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7588,"questionDisplayText":"Remove Old Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you need an old pool removed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11555,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7589,"questionDisplayText":"Pool features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any pool features you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11556,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden decking","answerDisplayText":"Wooden decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Covers","answerDisplayText":"Covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11558,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting systems","answerDisplayText":"Lighting systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11559,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool entry / exit steps","answerDisplayText":"Pool entry / exit steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11560,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","answerDisplayText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heating systems","answerDisplayText":"Heating systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11562,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7585,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Provided by Customer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the pool for this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7586,"questionDisplayText":"Type of pool install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of above ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","answerDisplayText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","answerDisplayText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11547,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","answerDisplayText":"Soft sided pool (vinyl)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11549,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","answerDisplayText":"Hard sided pool (metal or resin)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7587,"questionDisplayText":"Shape of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What shape of above ground pool do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11550,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11551,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rectangle","answerDisplayText":"Rectangle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11552,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11550,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11551,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rectangle","answerDisplayText":"Rectangle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11552,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7588,"questionDisplayText":"Remove Old Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you need an old pool removed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11555,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11555,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7589,"questionDisplayText":"Pool features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any pool features you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11556,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden decking","answerDisplayText":"Wooden decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Covers","answerDisplayText":"Covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11558,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting systems","answerDisplayText":"Lighting systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11559,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool entry / exit steps","answerDisplayText":"Pool entry / exit steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11560,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","answerDisplayText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heating systems","answerDisplayText":"Heating systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11562,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11556,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wooden decking","answerDisplayText":"Wooden decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Covers","answerDisplayText":"Covers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11558,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting systems","answerDisplayText":"Lighting systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11559,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool entry / exit steps","answerDisplayText":"Pool entry / exit steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11560,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","answerDisplayText":"Fencing / safety enclosure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11561,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heating systems","answerDisplayText":"Heating systems","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11562,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}